phantomgourmet.com 2016-05-13

# Privacy Policy

The personal data collected automatically by PhantomGourmet.com, the Phantom Gourmet Facebook App or entered voluntarily by the users is treated according to the procedures listed here below. We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. We ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using PhantomGourmet.com restaurant search.  

**Information we collect**

**Personal data collected when login by Facebook**  
Basic information and likes on Facebook

**How do we collect and use the information**  
User registration  
PhantomGourmet.com collects your email, name for signup related features and if used by the Facebook app your basic information and likes.

**Google Analytics** (Google)  
PhantomGourmet.com also uses Google Analytics . Google Analytics is a web analysis service supplied by Google, Inc., which utilizes cookies by means of which it collects Personal Information on the User, which is forwarded to, and deposited on, Google's servers in the United States. Google utilizes this information in order to track and examine your use of the website, to prepare reports on the activities of the website for the website operators and to supply other services relevant to the activities of the website and to the use of the Internet. Google does not associate the user's IP address with any other information in Google's possession. Any refusal to utilize the cookies, by selecting the appropriate setup on your browser, may prevent the use of all the functions of this website.

**Facebook social buttons/widgets** (Facebook)  
This is a service run by Facebook Inc., a company that complies with the Safe Harbor Privacy Policy Framework initiative, guaranteeing the handling of Personal Information in compliance with security standards. The service allows the User to interact with the social network via this website. Facebook, through the User click, acquires information about his/her/its visit to the Site. Facebook does not share any information or data in its possession with the Site or the Data Controller. For further information on the use of Personal Information by Facebook Inc., please consult the following link: http://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation.php

**Twitter social buttons/widgets** (Twitter)  
This is a service supplied by Twitter, a company that complies with the Safe Harbor Privacy Policy Framework initiative, guaranteeing the handling of Personal Information in compliance with security standards. By simply clicking on the Twitter push-button on the Site ("Twitter Button"), the service makes it possible share liking of Phantom Gourmet on Twitter.com For further information on the use of the Personal Information by the Twitter Button service offered by Twitter, please consult the following link http://twitter.com/privacy.

**Social Applications**  
Facebook app  
These services allow PhantomGourmet.com to access the basic data on your profile in Facebook, and likes. These services are not activated automatically, but require authorization by the user. This is a service managed by Facebook Inc., For further information on the use of Personal Information by Facebook Inc.: http://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation.php

**How we protect users information:**

**Security**  
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. While no data transmission over the internet is 100% secure from intrusion, in order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we maintain commercially suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure your personal information. However, regardless of our efforts and the device you use to access our services, it is possible that third parties may, unlawfully, intercept or access transmissions or private communications over an unsecured transmission.
